sitelevel.com 2007-07-08

# siteLevel - Privacy Policy

|  |   
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  | 1. |  | Overview  
---|---|---  
|  | siteLevel is a service offered by whatUseek, Corp. that enables companies and individuals to enable their web sites with a site search engine - allowing visitors to the given web site to search only within that site.  This Privacy Policy addresses the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information about persons or entities that sign-up for a siteLevel account.  
|  |    
2. |  | Information That We Collect  
|  | Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a user-friendly and customized experience.  This applies to both the operation of your siteLevel account as well as our effort to support you in managing your account.

  Personal information of users is collected both in the registration and account management areas.  Such information includes contact information (name, telephone, address, etc.), as well as information regarding the structure of your web site.

  For users purchasing the siteLevel Pro service, you may also provide financial information (i.e. credit card billing information) for the billing of your subscription.

  In addition, we collect various types of information through the use of "cookies."  The uses of such information includes ensuring that registration and account management sessions are secure.  Other information collected through cookies includes, but is not limited to, the origin from where you accessed the siteLevel web site when initially registering.

  whatUseek also records information about how its users interact with the siteLevel web site, both in the general and member areas.  Such information is used to help improve the content and user-friendliness of the site.  
  
|  |    
3. |  | Our Use Of Your Information  
|  | We use personally identifiable information about you (as a siteLevel user) to facilitate the services that you request.  We use information that we collect about you to customize your siteLevel service, to support your in managing your account, and to help improve the siteLevel service to better meet the needs of our users.  If you choose to purchase the siteLevel Pro service (a paid-for service), we use your address and billing information to bill you and provide associated support.

  You agree that we may use the information that we have about you to improve our marketing and promotional activities, to analyze site activity, improve our offerings, aid in supporting you in using the service, and customize our site's content and services.  
  
|  |    
4. |  | Advertisers  
|  | whatUseek collects personally identifiable information and discloses such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes.  In such situations, we do not disclose to these third parties any information that could be used to identify you personally.  
|  |    
5. |  | Internal Service Providers  
|  | We use internal service providers to facilitate our services (such as credit card processors and merchant banks) and therefore we provide some of your personally identifiable information directly to them if appropriate.  
|  |    
6. |  | Legal Requests  
|  | whatUseek cooperates with law enforcement agencies and other third parties to enforce laws.  You agree to authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government agencies as we, in our sole discretion, determine to be necessary or appropriate, as it relates to investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, piracy, or other activities that are illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.  
|  |    
7. |  | Our Disclosure Of Your Information  
|  |  | Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all private information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this Privacy Policy.  One example of this would be a court order to disclose such information.  Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise that your personal information will always remain private.

  As a matter of policy, we DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.  However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed:  
  
---  
|  |    
8. |  | Control Of Your Password  
|  | You are responsible for all actions taken with your user ID (email address) and password, including any fees incurred by these actions.  Therefore, we strongly recommend that you do not disclose your siteLevel user ID and password to any third parties.  If you choose to share your user ID and password with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your user ID and password.  If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf.  Therefore, if the security of your password becomes compromised, you should immediately change your password.  
|  |    
9. |  | Security  
|  | whatUseek uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information.  We employ various methods to protect such data from unauthorized access.  However, on the Internet, there is no foolproof method of keeping information 100% secure.  
|  |    
10. |  | Notice  
|  | We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by publishing such ameded terms on our site.  All amended terms shall become effective automatically 30 days after they are initially posted on our site.  
|  |    
|  |
